[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie, The Notebook, Noah is occasionally shown as an old man, who does what to help Allie overcome her medical condition?", "correct_answer": "Read a story to her", "incorrect_answers": ["Take her on a boat ride", "Show her pictures", "Take her back to their house"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American shoe company, that offered a job to basketball player Chuck Taylor, was opened  in Malden, Massachusetts in 1908.", "correct_answer": "Converse", "incorrect_answers": ["Nike", "Airbound", "Rebound"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does Craig say he plays for when asked if he plays sports by the mailman in Next Friday?", "correct_answer": "Cucamunga Cracker-Killers", "incorrect_answers": ["Cracker Killers", "Chimichanga Killers", "Cockaroach Killers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following actors were not in the movie The Crow?", "correct_answer": "Christian Slater", "incorrect_answers": ["John Polito", "Bai Ling", "Angel David"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following fears is not of a color?", "correct_answer": "Mageirocophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Leukophobia", "Xanthophobia", "Porphyrophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of soup is the popular Italian soup Minestrone?", "correct_answer": "Vegetable soup", "incorrect_answers": ["Cold soup", "Fish soup", "Lamb soup"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was there ever any evidence found after 1936 that Thylacines may have still been living in Australia?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Guess the missing number in the following sequence: 15, 30, 40, ___, 90, 180, 190.", "correct_answer": "80", "incorrect_answers": ["55", "45", "50"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The carrot is thought to have originated from this country.", "correct_answer": "Afghanistan", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "China", "Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the capital and the largest city in North Korea?", "correct_answer": "Pyongyang", "incorrect_answers": ["Nampho", "Hungnam", "Sinuiju"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This annually awarded architecture prize is usually referred to as \u2018The Nobel Prize for Architecture\u2019.", "correct_answer": "Pritzker Architecture Prize", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Jefferson Medal", "Aga Khan Award", "Stirling Prize"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the palace where Indiana Jones and Co. end up in the movie Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom?", "correct_answer": "Pankot Palace", "incorrect_answers": ["New Delhi Palace", "Shankara Palace", "It has no name."]}]